A Guide to the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Administration, Records, 1997-2006 (bulk 2002-2006)
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Virginia Office of the Secretary of Administration 1997-2006 (bulk 2002-2006)
The Library of Virginia
42402
30 cu. ft. (86 boxes)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Privacy protected information is considered closed for 100 years after date of record creation. Types of records restricted include, but are not limited to: medical information, social security numbers, employee performance reviews, employee grievance materials, and attorney-client privileged documents. Restricted material has been sealed but has not been removed from the collection.
Acquisition Information
Transferred by Faye K. Straub, Office of the Secretary of Administration, 1111 East Broad Street, Room 307-B, Richmond, Virginia, 23219, 16 January 2006.
Biographical/Historical Information
The Office of Administration was established in 1966 as part of the Office of the Governor to assist the Chief Executive in carrying out his duties. Several agencies including the divisions of the Budget, Personnel, Engineering and Building and Planning reported to the Commissioner of Administration. In 1970, the Governor's Management Commission Study recommended the creation of six "Deputy Governors" to assist the Chief Executive in his managerial duties. Compatible functions of government were grouped under these administrative heads, who would serve as the Governor's top management team or "secretariats," as they are now called. Governor Linwood Holton's top priority for the 1972 session of the General Assembly was a proposal for a Governor's Cabinet, reorganizing state agencies into six major departments, each headed by a secretary appointed by the Governor. The office of the Secretary of Administration was created on April 8, 1972, by an act passed by the General Assembly. Governor Holton appointed T. Edward Temple, the Commissioner of Administration since 1970, as the first Secretary of Administration. When Temple took office on July 1, 1972, he was responsible for the divisions of the Budget, Personnel, Engineering and Buildings, Automated Data Processing, Justice and Crime Prevention, State Planning and Community Affairs, Council on the Environment, State Board of Elections and the Office of Special Programs. The Office has undergone a series of administrative reorganizations since 1972. On April 12, 1976, the Legislature combined the secretariats for administration and finance, effective July 1, 1976. On July 1, 1984, the offices were separated.
The Secretary of Administration is a member of the Governor's Cabinet, is appointed by the governor, and is subject to confirmation by the General Assembly. At the start of Governor Mark R. Warner's term in 2002, the Secretary of Administration was responsible for the direction of, or had jurisdiction over, 12 state agencies and boards. Three entities were removed from the Secretary of Administration's supervision during Governor Warner's term, and two agencies received changes in title. The original list of agencies and boards under the heading of the Secretary of Administration is as follows: Charitable Gaming Commission (name changed to the Department of Charitable Gaming in 2003), Commonwealth Competition Council (transferred to the Department of Budget and Planning in June 2004), Compensation Board, State Board of Elections, Department of Employment Dispute Resolution, Department of General Services, Department of Human Resource Management, Council on Human Rights, Commission on Local Government (merged with the Department of Housing and Community Development in 2003), Public Broadcasting Board, Department of Rights for Virginians with Disabilities (became an independent agency called the Virginia Office for Protection and Advocacy in 2002), and the Department of Veterans' Affairs, (name changed to the Department of Veterans Services in 2003).
On January 3, 2002 Governor-elect Warner named Sandra Bowen as his Secretary of Administration. Prior to taking this position, Secretary Bowen served as Special Assistant to Governor Charles S. Robb, and as Secretary of the Commonwealth during the administration of Governor Gerald L. Baliles. She was also the Director of Gubernatorial Transition between the Robb and Baliles administrations. Sheryl D. Bailey, formerly of the Hampton city manager's office, and James T. Roberts, formerly the Director of Planning and Resources at the Science Museum of Virginia were selected as Deputy Secretaries of Administration. Roberts later became Director of the Department of General Services, and Richard Zorn was selected to fill his position as Deputy Secretary. Information about this office is available in the archived website files of the Office of the Secretary of Administration, (2005-2006). They can be found by searching the Library of Virginia's catalog using "Secretary of Administration" as the subject.
Scope and Content
Correspondence, reports, reviews, memorandums and other working papers created and collected by the Office of the Secretary of Administration during the gubernatorial term of Virginia Governor Mark R. Warner, 2002-2006. This collection consists of 17 records series which document the activities of the Office of the Secretary of Administration, as well as the agencies and boards which fall under its heading.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Agency Employees on Temporary Assignment Reports, 2002-2005
Series II. Appointment Calendars, 2002-2005
Series III. Assessments of Mandates on Local Government, 2002-2005
Series IV. Capital Outlay Files, 2002-2005
Series V. Constituent Correspondence, 2002-2005
Series VI. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation: Assigned State Agencies, 2001-2005
Series VII. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation: Office of the Secretary, 2001-2005
Series VIII. Environmental Impact Studies, 2002-2005
Series IX. Freedom of Information Act Requests, 2002-2005
Series X. Intellectual Property Rights, 2002-2005
Series XI. Legislative Files, 2002-2006
Series XII. Public Broadcasting Board, 1997-2006
Series XIII. Real Property Files, 2002-2005
Series XIV. Special Projects File: Electronic Procurement (eVA), 2002-2005
Series XV. Special Projects File: Virginia Partners in Procurement, 2003-2004
Series XVI. Veterans' Affairs Records, 2002-2005
Series XVII. Weekly Report Files, 2002-2005
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Separated Material
One folder of oversize material from the series titled "Correspondence and Supporting Documentation: Office of the Secretary," and its folder labeled "Public Safety, Dept. of--Corrections, Dept. of: Staunton Correctional Center," can be found in map case 24, drawer 1. (See separation notice in folder).
Contents List
- Series I. Agency Employees on Temporary Assignment Reports, 2002-2005., Extent: 4 folders. (Box 1)
  Consists of documentation tracking the activities of state employees temporarily assigned to the Governor's cabinet.
  - Employee Temporary Assignment Reports, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Employee Temporary Assignment Reports, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Employee Temporary Assignment Reports, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Employee Temporary Assignment Reports, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Series II. Appointment Calendars, 2002-2005., Extent: 1 folder. (Box 1)
  Contains the monthly appointment calendars of Sandra Bowen, Secretary of Administration.
  - Appointment Calendars (Sandra Bowen), 2002-2005 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Series III. Assessments of Mandates on Local Government, 2002-2005., Extent: 20 folders. (Box 1-2)
  Documents the work of the Commission on Local Government. This agency cataloged all state and federal mandates on local governments. The Commission compiled reports on these mandates, which were reviewed and signed by the Governor. Included in the documentation are completed assessments, background on the Mandates Cataloging and Assessment Program, reassessments, scheduling material, service awards, commission appointments, the Report on the Comparative Revenue Capacity, Revenue Effort, and Fiscal Stress of Virginia's Counties and Cities, 2000-2001, and information on the 2003 merger of the Commission with the Department of Housing and Community Development.
  - Assessments Completed, 2002 February-April (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Assessments Completed, 2002 June-August (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Assessments Completed, 2002 September-November (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Assessments Completed, 2002 December (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Assessments Completed, 2003 February-May (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Assessments Completed, 2003 July-September (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Assessments Completed, 2003 October-November (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Assessments Completed, 2004 January-April (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Assessments Completed, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Big Stone Gap/County of Wise Annexation Issue, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Commission Appointment, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Mandates Cataloging and Assessment Program Background Information, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Merger with Department of Housing and Community Development, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Reassessments, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Report on the Comparative Revenue Capacity, Revenue Effort, and Fiscal Stress of Virginia's Counties and Cities (2002-2001), 2003 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Request for Modification of Scheduled Assessment Period, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Scheduling Material, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Scheduling Material, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Scheduling Material, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Service Awards, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Series IV. Capital Outlay Files, 2002-2005., Extent: 18 folders. (Box 2-4)
  Contains subject files that document the funding, maintenance and operation of certain state buildings. Most of the files contain a Memorandum of Understanding for Delegation of Certain Real Estate Approvals and Capital Outlay Responsibilities as they pertain to Virginia's public universities. These memos document the pilot program for delegated authority for non-general fund capital projects and expense leases.
  - Christopher Newport University, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - George Mason University, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - George Mason University, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - James Madison University, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - James Madison University, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Old Dominion University, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Radford University, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Polytechnic and State University, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Polytechnic and State University, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Virginia, University of, 2002-2004 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Virginia, University of, 2002-2004 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Virginia, University of, 2002-2004 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - William and Mary, College of, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - William and Mary, College of, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Series V. Constituent Correspondence, 2002-2005., Extent: 132 folders. (Box 5-17)
  Contains constituent correspondence pertaining to all agencies overseen by the Office of the Secretary of Administration. Most of the letters were originally addressed to Governor Warner, but were assigned to the Secretary of Administration for response. The files cover topics including the 2002 state budget crisis, veterans' issues, the use of electronic voting machines in Virginia, changes to the state's healthcare plan and other employment-related issues, and problems surrounding the eVA procurement system. The files are arranged alphabetically by year. At the end of each year there are usually a few subject files. The F.Y.I. Files contain correspondence that was sent to Secretary Bowen's office from other Secretariats for her review. In the 2004 correspondence, there are several folders devoted to correspondence surrounding the proposed demolition of the Eighth and Ninth Street buildings, as well as a pay increase for state employees.
  - A, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Ba-Bo, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Br-Bu, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Ca-Cl, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Co-Cu, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - D, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - E, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - F, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - G, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Ha, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - He-Hu, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - I, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - J, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - K, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - L, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Mc, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Ma-Mi, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Mo-My, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - N, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - O, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - P, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - R, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Sa-Si, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Sm-Sw, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - T, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - V, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - W, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Y-Z, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Unanswered or Re-routed Mail (B-H), 2002 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Unanswered or Re-routed Mail (K-W), 2002 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - F.Y.I. File, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - A, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Ba-Bi, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Blagojevich, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Blal-Bu, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - C, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - D, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - E, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - F, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Ga-Ge, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Gi-Gw, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Ha-Hi, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Ho-Hy, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - I, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - J, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - K, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - L, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Mc, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Ma-Me, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Mi-My, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - N, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - O, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - P, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Ra-Ri, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Ro-Ru, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Sa-Sh, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Si-Sw, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - T, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - V, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Wa-We, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Wh-Wr, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Y-Z, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - F.Y.I. File (B-K), 2003 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - F.Y.I. File (M-W), 2003 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Ad-Am, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - An-Ay, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Ba-Bl, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Bo-Bu, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Ca-Cl, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Co-Cy, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - D, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - E, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - F, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - G, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Ha-He, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Hi-Hy, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - I, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - J, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - K, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - L, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Mc, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Ma-Me, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Mi-Mu, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - N, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - O, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - P, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Q, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Ra-Ri, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Ro-Ru, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Sa-Si, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Sl-Sw, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - T, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - U, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - V, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Wa-Wh, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Wi-Wy, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Y, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Eighth and Ninth Street Office Buildings, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - F.Y.I. File (A-L), 2004 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - F.Y.I. File (M-T), 2004 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Pay Increase for State Employees (A-P), 2004 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Pay Increase for State Employees (Q-W), 2004 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - A, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Ba-Be, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Bl-By, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Ca-Cl, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Co-Cu, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Da, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - De-Du, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - E, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - F, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - G, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Ha-He, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Hi-Hu, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - J, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - K, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - L, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Mc, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Ma, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Me-My, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - N, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - O, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - P, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - R, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Sa-Sh, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Si-Su, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - T, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - V, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Wa-We, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Wi-Wy, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Z, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - F.Y.I. File, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Series VI. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation: Assigned State Agencies, 2001-2005., Extent: 70 folders. (Box 18-26)
  Contains files composed of correspondence (constituent and internal), along with supporting material such as reports, proposals, and other working papers. Several state agencies operated under the Office of the Secretary of Administration. These agencies were referred to as "assigned" agencies. The assigned agencies of the Office of the Secretary of Administration documented here are the Department of Charitable Gaming, the Compensation Board, the Commonwealth Competition Council, the State Board of Elections, the Department of Employment Dispute Resolution, the Department of General Services, the Department of Human Resource Management, the Council on Human Rights, the Department of Rights of Virginians with Disabilities, the Governor's Office of Support Services, and the Virginia War Memorial Foundation. The files are arranged alphabetically by agency. Many of the agencies have several folders, some containing information from a specific timeframe. Others contain material describing a particular topic, and some document the activities of a division within a certain agency. At the end of this series there is a folder containing correspondence from the Office of the Secretary of Administration to the agency heads, as well as another folder containing correspondence to all state employees, agency heads, and the other Secretaries.
  Notable files include those related to the State Board of Elections and the implementation of the new Virginia Election and Registration Information System (VERIS). Also of note are files pertaining to the Virginia Administrative Dispute Resolution Act (VADRA), found in the Department of Employment Dispute Resolution material, which document pilot programs put in place to help agencies resolve internal disputes. Within the Department of General Services material there is a significant amount of information on the Public-Private Education Facilities and Infrastructure Act (PPEA), which allows for expedited construction and renovation projects. Also under the Department of General Services heading are several folders of material that document issues arising from the Small, Women-owned and Minority Businesses (SWAM) procurement initiative, designed to ensure that historically underutilized businesses gain access to state contracting opportunities.
  - Agency Heads (Correspondence to), 2002-2005 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - All State Employees, Agency Heads of Secretaries (Correspondence to), 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Charitable Gaming Commission, 2001-2003 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Charitable Gaming Commission, 2001-2003 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Charitable Gaming Commission--JLARC Review, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Charitable Gaming Commission--JLARC Review, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Charitable Gaming, Dept. of, 2003-2005 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Charitable Gaming, Dept. of, 2003-2005 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Charitable Gaming, Dept. of, 2003-2005 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Commonwealth Competition Council, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Commonwealth Competition Council, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Compensation Board, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Compensation Board, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Compensation Board, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Compensation Board, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Compensation Board, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Compensation Board, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Compensation Board, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Compensation Board, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Compensation Board, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Compensation Board, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Compensation Board, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Elections, State Board of, 2002-2005 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Elections, State Board of, 2002-2005 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Elections, State Board of, 2002-2005 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Elections, State Board of, 2002-2005 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Elections, State Board of, 2002-2005 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Elections, State Board of--Unisys Contract and Activities, 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Elections, State Board of--Unisys Contract and Activities, 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Elections, State Board of--Unisys Contract and Activities, 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Employment Dispute Resolution, Dept. of, 2002-2004 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Employment Dispute Resolution, Dept. of--Administrative Dispute Resolution Council, 2002-2005 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Employment Dispute Resolution, Dept. of--Administrative Dispute Resolution Council, 2002-2005 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - General Services, Dept. of--Fleet Management Services, 2002-2005 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - General Services, Dept. of--Fleet Management Services, 2002-2005 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - General Services, Dept. of--License Plate Sheeting, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - General Services, Dept. of--License Plate Sheeting, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - General Services, Dept. of--License Plate Sheeting, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - General Services, Dept. of--Mail Consolidation Project, 2003-2005 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - General Services, Dept. of--Parking, 2002-2004 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - General Services, Dept. of--Public-Private Education Facilities and Infrastructure Act (PPEA), 2002-2005 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - General Services, Dept. of--Public-Private Education Facilities and Infrastructure Act (PPEA), 2002-2005 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - General Services, Dept. of--Shenandoah Regional Laboratory, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - General Services, Dept. of--Small, Women-owned and Minority Businesses (SWAM), 2004 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - General Services, Dept. of--Small, Women-owned and Minority Businesses (SWAM), 2004 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - General Services, Dept. of--Small, Women-owned and Minority Businesses (SWAM), 2004 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Human Resource Management, Dept. of, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Human Resource Management, Dept. of, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Human Resource Management, Dept. of, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Human Resource Management, Dept. of, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Human Resource Management, Dept. of, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Human Resource Management, Dept. of, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Human Resource Management, Dept. of, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Human Resource Management, Dept. of--CVC Campaign, 2002-2004 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Human Resource Management, Dept. of--CVC Campaign, 2002-2004 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Human Resource Management, Dept. of--Health Care, 2002-2005 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Human Resource Management, Dept. of--Health Care, 2002-2005 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Human Resource Management, Dept. of--Telecommuting, 2002-2005 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Human Resource Management, Workers' Compensation, 2002-2003 (Box 26, Folder 3)